<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>XeroLinux H.Q on </title>
    <link>https://xerolinux.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in XeroLinux H.Q on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://xerolinux.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://xerolinux.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xerolinux.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>Description With XeroLinux no longer being a Distro, but a collection of Projects/Scripts, created with a simple goal in mind, making ArchLinux more approachable, easier to install and configure. That&amp;rsquo;s if you choose to use it, or even give it a try.&#xA;ArchLinux / KDE Plasma I have so many great ideas in the pipeline, it&amp;rsquo;s crazy ! I love working with ArchLinux. It&amp;rsquo;s the most flexible Distro I have ever had the pleasure to work with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>https://xerolinux.xyz/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xerolinux.xyz/projects/</guid>
      <description>The Toolkit. This toolkit aims to be an all-in-one solution for post-installation, expediting your Arch setup. Please head on over to toolkit&amp;rsquo;s Github Page and check out the Wiki for more detailed information.&#xA;Xero-Layan Rice It&amp;rsquo;s the best KDE rice I have ever created, in my opinion. If you want to enjoy said rice on your system, feel free to teleport to Github and have fun. 😀&#xA;Xero-Plasma Install Script With the help of this script you will be able to install Plasma in one of 4 methods as you can see in the image below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socials</title>
      <link>https://xerolinux.xyz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xerolinux.xyz/contact/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Ok, so, if you want to ask me questions about my projects directly, you can do so by either joining the XeroLinux Forum or via the Mastodon instance. I will also mention that I have a Discord Server set up, if you feel like joining it, please do.&#xA;YouTube Project also has a YouTube Channel where I try my best to put out a new video every week on Wednesday, talking about ArchLinux and various ways I work on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://xerolinux.xyz/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xerolinux.xyz/support/</guid>
      <description>Support Me / My Cause If you want to see our projects thrive and continue, please do consider supporting them. Without your support none of this would have been possible. I thank every one of you who have pleged a few pennies here n there.&#xA;So, if you want to support me financially, there are 2 ways to do so currently. You can either do it via Ko-Fi or by becoming a Github-Sponsor</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
